Suraj ki baho mein ab
zindagi good morning and marriage
ki baa ab ye
zindagi roshan
[Music]
[Praise]
Sayo
[Praise] If you do
n't know then you will have to learn
ok from today you both are underwriters and you
in the case arre babu bhaiya someone is asking the price of the fish
I am saying what are you
saying babu two and you are there it is
raining a lot of happiness everywhere
[Music]
Meng elimination happen after every activity every time vahan pe ok go nite g motion
i speed se kise slowly slowly
[Music] slowly very nice very nice very nice
[Praise]
now this has become a custom okay chach ever is
a winning team we go play some music we are going to entertain all of us
Suraj ki baho mein ab ye zindagi ke rayne hai saason mein bato me roshan
[Praise]
[Music]
they are after every activity every time
as i